const STORE = [
  {
    question: 'When was the first official American hot sauce produced?',
    answers: [
      '1976',
      '1807',
      '1853',
      '1602'
    ],
    correctAnswer:
     '1807'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the current hottest pepper in the world?',
    answers: [
      'Ghost pepper',
      'Scorpion pepper',
      'Habaneros',
      'Carolina Reaper'
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      'Carolina Reaper'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is capsaicin?',
    answers: [
      'The oil in hot peppers that causes the feeling of heat',
      'How hot the peppers look while they are growing',
      'The amount of nutrients needed to grow the pepper',
      'how much the pepper seeds can yield on re-growth'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 
      'The oil in hot peppers that causes the feeling of heat'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was the Bhut Jolokia pepper used for?',
    answers: [
      'Home defense',
      'An extra kick for meals',
      'Keeping elephants from eating your crops',
      'Keeping bugs off of your crops'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 
      'Keeping elephants from eating your crops'
  },
  {
    question: 'What does SHU stand for?',
    answers: [
      'Super-hot unit',
      'Skeptic helium under',
      'Sensational helix under',
      'Scoville heat unit'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 
      'Scoville heat unit'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the 60 second record for most reaper peppers eaten?',
    answers: [
      '7',
      '107 grams',
      '120 grams',
      '15'
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      '120 grams'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who invented the Carolina Reaper pepper?',
    answers: [
      'Grace Hernandez',
      'John Knots',
      'Jocelyn Edwards',
      'Ed Currie'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 
      'Ed Currie'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is an heirloom pepper seed?',
    answers: [
      'A seed that has been mass produced and is stable',
      'A stable, open breed that has been going for generations',
      'A very old pepper seed',
      'A weird magic seed your Grandpa gave to you'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 
      'A stable, open breed that has been going for generations'
  },
  {
    question: 'How tall can a scorpion pepper plant grow?',
    answers: [
      '2 feet',
      '6 feet',
      '1.5 feet',
      '4 feet'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 
      '4 feet'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is one benefit eating hot peppers offer?',
    answers: [
      'Sweating toxins out of your body',
      'The oil in the peppers helps your skin health',
      'Decreasing inflammation of your cells',
      'Getting sufficient protein into your diet'

    ],
    correctAnswer: 
    'Decreasing inflammation of your cells'
  }
]
